{    
    "quizQuestions" :[
    {
        "question": "Who is the champion that can go back in time?",
        "answers": {
            "a" : "Shaco",
            "b" : "Lissandra",
            "c" : "Ekko",
            "d" : "Gnar"
        },
        "rightAnswer" : "c"
    },
    {
        "question":"Where is Garen from?",
        "answers": {
            "a" : "Freljord",
            "b" : "Noxus",
            "c" : "Zaun",
            "d" : "Demacia"
        },
        "rightAnswer" : "d"
    },
    {
        "question":"How is Fizz Ultimate Skill Called?",
        "answers": {
            "a" : "Chum the Waters",
            "b" : "Big Shark",
            "c" : "Urchin Strike",
            "d" : "Playful / Trickster"
        },
        "rightAnswer" : "a"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which champion has the highest base HP at level 1 with no items, runes, or masteries equipped?",
        "answers": {
            "a" : "Trundle",
            "b" : "Alistar",
            "c" : "Garen",
            "d" : "Tryndamere"
        },
        "rightAnswer" : "d"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which Yasuo’s Ability is called Steel Tempest?",
        "answers": {
            "a" : "q",
            "b" : "w",
            "c" : "e",
            "d" : "r"
        },
        "rightAnswer" : "a"
    },
    {
        "question":"Who is that Champion?",
        "answers": {
            "a" : "Morgana",
            "b" : "Lissandra",
            "c" : "Ashe",
            "d" : "Vi"
        },
        "rightAnswer" : "d"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which Champion was released in February, 2016?",
        "answers": {
            "a" : "Ekko",
            "b" : "Aurelion Sol",
            "c" : "Jhin",
            "d" : "Ornn"
        },
        "rightAnswer" : "c"
    },
    {
        "question":"How many Champions are in League Of Legends (Jan, 2019)?",
        "answers": {
            "a" : "140",
            "b" : "142",
            "c" : "144",
            "d" : "143"
        },
        "rightAnswer" : "d"
    },
    {
        "question":"“Wealth is my kind of burden” Whose is that quote?",
        "answers": {
            "a" : "Sivir",
            "b" : "LeBlanc",
            "c" : "Galio",
            "d" : "Twisted Fate"
        },
        "rightAnswer" : "a"
    },
    {
        "question":"“It's not how much time you have, it's ____ you use it” Fill Ekkos Sentence!",
        "answers": {
            "textInput": ""
        },
        "rightAnswer" : "how"
    }
]
}